Seven sisters. One identity.
What Happened to Monday is a science fiction, thriller,
mystery film directed by Tommy Wirkola.
In a world where families are limited to one child due to overpopulation, a set of identical septuplets must avoid being put to a
long sleep by the government and dangerous infighting while investigating the disappearance of one of their own.
The Settman Siblings, played by Noomi Rapace.
Nicolette Cayman, played by Glenn Close.
Terrence Settman, played by Willem Dafoe.
Adrian Knowles, played by Marwan Kenzari.
Joe, played by Christian Rubeck.
Jerry, played by Pål Sverre Hagen.
What Happened to Monday (known in several territories as Seven Sisters) is a 2017 science-fiction
action film directed by Tommy Wirkola and written by Max Botkin and Kerry Williamson.
The film stars Noomi Rapace, Glenn Close and Willem Dafoe.
What Happened to Monday was released theatrically in Europe and Asia, with Netflix distributing the
film in the United States, United Kingdom, and Latin America on August 18, 2017.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of chase, dystopia,
investigation, fake identity, overpopulation.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.